export const navLinks = [
  {
    id: 1,
    href: 'robotics',
    link: 'Robotics',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    href: 'coding',
    link: 'Coding',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    href: 'maths',
    link: 'Mathematics',
  },
];

export const categories = [
  {
    id: 1,
    image: '/assets/images/robotics.webp',
    category: 'Robotics',
    description: `Children learn about engineering, technology, and programming while exploring the world of robots. Building their own robots through practical activities, sharpening their analytical and problem-solving skills.`,
    link: '/robotics',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    image: '/assets/images/coding.webp',
    category: 'Coding',
    description:
      'Re-Learn teaches Coding for Kids and introduces children to computer programming, teaching them the basics of coding through interactive activities and projects that foster creativity and problem-solving skills.',
    link: '/coding',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    image: '/assets/images/maths.webp',
    category: 'Mathematics',
    description:
      'Mathematics is an important life skill which helps children in developing their cognitive abilities. We teach children mental shortcuts and calculation techniques to solve mathematical problems quickly and effectively.',
    link: '/maths',
  },
];

export const courses = [
  {
    id: 1,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Design',
    title: 'The Complete Web Design Course',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Development',
    title: 'FullStack Web Development Course',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Development',
    title: 'Python Beginner to Advanced Course',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Design',
    title: 'UI/UX Design Crazy Course With Harrys',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    image: '',
    category: 'AI Development',
    title: 'AI Development With Python (complete beginner course)',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Design',
    title: 'The Complete Web Design Course',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Design',
    title: 'The Complete Web Design Course',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    image: '',
    category: 'Web Design',
    title: 'The Complete Web Design Course',
  },
];

export const roboticsPricing = [
  {
    type: 'Starter',
    perClassPrice: 700,
    duration: 3,
    includes: [
      'Spark your interest in circuits, resistors, LEDs, and more!',
      'Design and develop 30+ projects using Electronics',
      'Projects Include: Electric Light & Switch, Sound Activated Switch, Musical Doorbell and more!',
    ],
    paymentLink: 'https://www.relernschool.in',
  },

  {
    type: 'Achiever',
    perClassPrice: 600,
    duration: 6,
    statement: 'Everything in Starter+',
    includes: [
      'Dive into a world of gears, pulleys, levers and more!',
      'Learn and develop 30+ projects using Electronics and Mechanics',
      'Projects Include: Construction Crane, Wind Mill, Crane, Hydraulic Lifting and More!',
    ],
    paymentLink: 'https://www.relernschool.in',
  },

  {
    type: 'Master',
    perClassPrice: 500,
    duration: 12,
    statement: 'Everything in Achiever+',
    includes: [
      'Discover the fascinating world of light, touch, sound, and distance sensors',
      'Get ready to revolutionize the way your robots sense and act!',
      'Develop 100+ projects with all the concepts you have learnt',
      'Chance to participate national and International Competitions',
    ],
    paymentLink: 'https://www.relernschool.in',
  },
];

export const roboticsAccordions = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: 'What courses does Relearn School offer?',
    answer: `Relearn School offers robotics, coding and Vedic Math's programs specifically designed for children, providing them with hands-on learning experience in these technological fields. `,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'How can I enroll in a course at Relearn School?',
    answer: `To enroll in a course at Relearn School, simply visit our website and complete the enrollment process for your chosen course. It's a straightforward online procedure that you can follow with ease. `,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Are the courses at Relearn School suitable for beginners?',
    answer: `Absolutely! Relearn School offers courses tailored for beginners and learners with diverse experience levels, making it an ideal choice for anyone looking to start their learning journey or enhance existing skills. `,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'How long are the training programs at Relearn School?',
    answer: `The duration of the training programs at Relearn School may vary depending on the course. Please refer to the course details for specific information. `,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      'Are the training programs at Relearn School available online or offline?',
    answer: `To accommodate learners' preferences and locations, Relearn School offers training programs in offline format with various flexible learning options.  `,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      'Does Relearn School provide certification upon completion of a course?',
    answer: `Yes, upon completing a course at Relearn School, you will receive a certificate that acknowledges your proficiency and expertise in the specific field of study. This certification is a testament to your skills and can enhance your career prospects. `,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Are the trainers at Relearn School experienced?',
    answer: `Certainly! The trainers at Relearn School are highly experienced professionals with expertise in their respective fields, ensuring they deliver quality education and guidance to all learners. `,
  },

  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      'What support is available if I face difficulties during the course?',
    answer: `Relearn School offers extensive support to students during the course, with accessible assistance through email or phone. Our devoted support staff responds to any issues or questions right away.`,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      'Does Relearn School offer any scholarships or financial assistance?',
    answer:
      'Relearn School potentially provides scholarships and financial aid to qualified individuals. Visit our website to learn more about our options or contact our support staff for more details. ',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'What are the accepted modes of payment at Relearn School?',
    answer:
      'Accepted modes of payment at Relearn School include Visa/MasterCard/Maestro Cards, Net Banking, Wallet, and UPI, providing multiple convenient options for students to pay their fees. ',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'What is the refund policy at Relearn School?',
    answer:
      'At Relearn School, there is a well-defined refund policy available in their Cancellation & Refund Policy document. For specific details, refer to the policy to understand the terms and conditions related to refunds.',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'How can I contact the support team at Relearn School?',
    answer: `Send an email to connect@skillsafari.in  contact the support staff at Relearn School. They will be happy to help you with any questions or concerns.  `,
  },
];
